# Garrett Stein-Seroussi

## **Full-Stack Web Developer**

Enthusiastic full-stack web developer eager to contribute to team success through hard work, attention to detail and excellent organizational skills. Clear understanding of front and back end development and training in Javascript, HTML, CSS, Node JS, Express, Sequelize, and more. Having spent many years working in various different fields, is now motivated to learn, grow and excel in a long term career in computer coding.

#### **SKILLS**

- Programming Languages
  - HTML
  - CSS
  - Javascript
  - JQuery

- Node JS
- Express
- Express-Handlebars
- Sequelize

- Proficient Spanish
- Conversation Arabic

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### The Animal Hospital of Carrboro, Carrboro, NC - Kennel Assistant

January 2016 - PRESENT

- Maintained clean and organized boarding areas to promote animal wellbeing.
- Contributed to client retention by consistently providing outstanding customer service to both clients and pets.

#### Movie Makers Inc, Durham, NC - Freelance Video Editor

March 2012 - December 2015

 Performed post-production work, including assembling raw material, editing sound and sequences and providing final product within time and budget constraints.

# UNC Student Stores, Chapel Hill, NC - Student Manager

March 2011 - December 2014

- Offered hands-on assistance to customers, assessing needs and maintaining current knowledge of consumer preferences.
- Coached employees and trained on methods for handling various aspects of sales, complicated issues and difficult customers.

# **EDUCATION**

## Coding Bootcamp at UNC-CH - Professional Certification

May 2020 - October 2020, Chapel Hill, NC

• A coding bootcamp that covers HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, Database Theory, MongoDB, MySQL, Git, C#, ASP.Net, and more.

# University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill

September 2012 - December 2014, Chapel Hill, NC

• Communications and Media Production